After delivering and validating, we will proceed to report the task.
I will also generate a TPA file for the report, and the generation method is similar to the one used during the analysis process.
After generating it, we will get a file like this.
I will hide the unnecessary columns.
Since this case requires MCDC, I will keep the MCDC column.
Alright, the result will look like this.
Now I will concatenate the data again.
I will fill in the necessary fields that need to be entered in the analysis file,
as well as in the tested database.
Okay, now I will do the concatenation.
For C modules, we will concatenate the item name and the check-in date.
For EXP modules, we will concatenate the item name and its version.
After that, I will check which modules were estimated at the beginning.
I will fill them in this Responsible column here.
Then I will use VLOOKUP between this file, the concat column, and the analysis file
Here is the analysis file.
Okay.
I will apply for MT_Needed, Tester_Comments, CRP_Comments, and CRP_Review_Status.
I will apply it to all rows.
I will filter the MT_Needed column.
Then I will put Responsible here.
These are the modules that have been tested and validated in this task, with a total of 63 items.
However, there are still some undefined modules here, and the tester has commented that
these modules were already tested but item changed the check-in date.
I'll check if there are any unusual comments here.
For example, this module was initially estimated and analyzed as a test module.
However, when testing, the tester checked it again and confirmed that it is a valid module.
So I will change this to Valid.
I will also update the corresponding CRP links.
Then I will clear the formula and paste it back as values.
Then, I'll update some statuses, changing them from "valid" to "validated".
Okay.
I will double-check the modules and remove the unnecessary values of those columns.
I also need to make sure that the related comments are still correct.
For modules with CRP link like this, they are usually modules whose coverage is below 100%.
I will fill in the reason for them using the comments from the MTComment column.
Next, I will test the remaining modules, excluding those that were just tested or have already been validated.
For the remaining modules, I will check whether they are marked as "undefined" and have no reason or comment.
Since they were already tested by Cantata from the beginning, and I already searched for them during the analysis phase, I will just map them here.
Okay, I will clear it and check one more time to see whether all undefined modules already had their reasons?
Okay, for these test modules, I will also put them here.
I will put the information here as Undefined.
Okay. I will put all of the coverage information into the comment cell.
For the modules that were changed check-in date.
It doesn't have the validation, so the results are not shown here.
So I will add the comment and search for the information.
I already searched for it in another file, so I will use VLOOKUP to do it faster.
Okay. Please check whether the information is complete.
All the tested information is included, including the check-in date,
the UT result and the reason attached in the comment.
Okay, I will check one more time to make sure all modules have their reasons.
Okay, everything is complete. Next, I will check the passed modules whose coverage is below 100% and find the reason for them.
Here, I will also use VLOOKUP to get the reason, based on the concat key, from the tested database file.
I will check it here first.
Then I will
filter the modules that already have a reason
and make them equal to this column.
For the cases that do not have a reason yet.
Okay, I will try to VLOOKUP to to find as many reasons as possible.
Similarly, I will check with C1.
This is MT Executed, and it is quite old.
Also, the origin and entity are from another team, so we don't need to care about it when there is no reason.
I will check it again one more time.
For the remaining reasons, we can see that some reasons look unusual.
For those cases, we will remove them from the comment.
There are only a few Vietnamese owners here.
But it is quite old, so we can skip it.
I will check it again.
I will check whether there are any comments for Not Applicable. No, there are none.
For the Undefined column, all reasons are already complete.
Next is the Pass below 100% column.
It seems to be complete as well.
Okay. I will paste it back as values.
Then I will delete the unnecessary columns.
I will keep only the columns
Tester Comment, CRP Comment, and CRP Review Status.
These 63 items are the modules that were either tested or validated in this task.
Okay, we can summarize that there are a total of 13 validated items and 50 tested items.
This matches the initial total of 63 items.